[{"id": 467, "question": "Teamwork is all about working together to achieve a common goal or purpose.Is teamwork out of date?Why it is so hard to effectively conduct teamwork in those things? One way we employ teamwork in everyday lives is by becoming a parent.It is a parent's job to teach their children the fundamental skills and give them the knowledge they need to be successful in life.So why is teamwork disappearing in this aspect of our lives?Well in today's society,we find that more and more parents are experiencing that the teamwork is one-sided thing.According to a 2009report from the US,there are 13.7million single parents raising their children in the US and this amount could be due to the fact that parents are not stepping up and taking responsibility for their children or they don't have the means to,so...\n\nQ: What is the author's main purpose of writing the passage?", "options": ["To show the importance of housework.", "To introduce how teamwork works now.", "To tell us the current economic recession.", "To show his attitude towards teamwork."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2266, "question": "People appear to be born to calculate. The numerical skills of children develop so early that it is easy to imagine an internal clock of mathematical maturity guiding their growth. Not long after learning to walk and talk, they can set the table with impressive accuracy--one plate, one knife, one spoon, one fork for each of the five chairs. Soon they are capable of noting that they have placed five knives, spoons and forks on the table, and a bit later, that this amounts to fifteen pieces of silverware. Having thus mastered addition, some people expect that if a child were on a desert island at birth and brought back seven years later, he or she could enter a second-grade mathematics class without any serious problems of intellectual adjustment. Of course, the truth is not so simple. This ...\n\nQ: From the passage we can know that children   _  .", "options": ["have an internal clock of mathematical maturity guiding their growth.", "begin to master simple counting soon after they learn to walk and talk.", "are born with numerical skills.", "can not understand abstract numbers."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1678, "question": "This is an excerpt from a speech by Steve Jobs, former CEO of Apple, delivered to graduates of Stanford University on June 12, 2005. I was lucky -- I found what I loved to do early in life. Woz and I started Apple in my parents' garage when I was 20. We worked hard, and in 10 years Apple had grown from just the two of us in a garage into a $2 billion company with over 4000 employees. We had just released our finest creation -- the Macintosh -- a year earlier, and I had just turned 30. And then I got fired. How can you get fired from a company you started? Well, as Apple grew we hired someone who I thought was very talented to run the company with me, and for the first year or so things went well. But then our visions of the future began to diverge(to be different) and eventually we had _ ....\n\nQ: Steve Jobs probably values   _   most according to his speech.", "options": ["patience", "faith", "inspiration", "luck"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2865, "question": "Be Healthy! Be Slim! Be Beautiful! Discover the secret for a Healthy, Slim, Beautiful You! Discover how to be Healthy, Slim and Beautiful! I love this healthy diet program because it helps you lose weight, lose inches, feel healthy and look beautiful. This healthy diet is an 8-week program which is unlike other diet regimes because it focuses on proper nutritional first and weight loss second. Your body must have proper levels of minerals, vitamins, and protein in order to work well. It provides a simply lifestyle change to give you more energy and improve your health most greatly. It offers control over stomach and continuing hunger with a calorie dense diet allowing 1,700 to 2,000 calories a day. If a person has a weight problem their body probably is not working at proper levels of basi...\n\nQ: What is this passage mainly about?", "options": ["How people should keep fit.", "A healthy diet program.", "Some healthy people.", "Ways to lose weight."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 765, "question": "\"To be or not to be.\" Outside the Bible, these six words are the most famous in all the literature of the world. They were spoken by Hamlet when he was thinking aloud, and they are the most famous words in Shakespeare because Hamlet was speaking not only for himself but also for every thinking man and woman. To be or not to be, to live or not to live, to live richly and abundantly, or to live dully and meanly. A philosopher once wanted to know whether he was alive or not, which is a good question for everyone to put to himself occasionally. He answered it by saying: \"I think, therefore I am.\" But the best definition of existence I ever saw was one written by another philosopher who said: \"To be is to be in relations.\" If this is true, then the more relations a living thing has, the more it...\n\nQ: Which of the following behavior is probably NOT encouraged by the author?", "options": ["Thinking more than your own business.", "Caring only about your physical welfare.", "Reading good novels.", "Listening to fine music."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 342, "question": "John Blanchard stood up from the bench, straightened his Army uniform, and studied the crowd of people making their way through Grand Central Station. He looked for the girl whose heart he knew, but whose face he didn't, the girl with the rose. His interest in her had begun thirteen months before in a Florida library. Taking a book off the shelf he found himself intrigued, not with the words of the book, but with the notes penciled in the margin. The soft handwriting reflected a thoughtful soul and insightful mind. In the front of the book, he discovered the previous owner's name, Miss Hollis Maynell. With time and effort he located her address. She lived in New York City. He wrote her a letter introducing himself and inviting her to correspond. The next day he was shipped overseas for ser...\n\nQ: When Blanchard went over to greet the woman, he was  _  .", "options": ["satisfied and confident", "disappointed but well - behaved", "annoyed and bad - mannered", "shocked but inspired"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1010, "question": "After the first World War, a small group of veterans returned to their village in Britain. Most of them managed to get along fairly well, but one--Francis Blustering, who had been wounded and who never recovered his strength-- was unable to work like others. In time he became very poor. Yet he was too proud to accept anything from the people in the village. Once, these veterans held a reunion dinner in the home of Jules Grandin, who had made a good deal of money. Grandin produced a curiosity --a large old gold coin. Each man examined it with interest as it passed around the long table. All, however, had drunk wine freely and the room was full of noisy talk, so that the gold piece was soon forgotten. Later, when Grandin remembered it and asked for it, the coin was missing. One of them sugge...\n\nQ: The coin was missing because   _  .", "options": ["all the friends were drunk", "the room was too noisy", "they were too excited to pay attention to it", "Blustering hid it in a secret place"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3021, "question": "For years we have been dieting strictly after the year-end overeating, afraid that when summer. comes, the bigger size we have accumulated will betray how we ate. Now scientists say, it's a little bug that causes obesity . As the holiday season with its abundant feasting arrives, millions of food lovers are keeping an eye on their figures. But scientists have found that weight gain is not about too much Christmas turkey or hot chocolates, but some bacteria in your guts . Chinese scientists recently discovered a type ofbacteria in guts that may be to blame for obesity. A research team led by Zhao Liping, a professor in Shanghai, has identified a precise link between a particular kind ofbacteria and unusual weight gain. \"The endotoxin released by the bacterium can activate a gene that helps ...\n\nQ: What can be learned from Zhao's research?", "options": ["Obesity is related to a kind of bacteria.", "Healthy diet helps reduce your fat.", "Chocolate doesn't cause weight gain.", "Too much food leads to overweight."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1704, "question": "My mom has eyes in the back of her head. She also taught me from an early age to be suspicious of strange men, especially when they give you presents. One day, a \"nice man\" bearing flowers managed to steal 20 euros from her purse, while she was holding it in her hands. \"He said he was collecting for a church charity so I pulled out a euro,\" she explains, \"He said 'no, no, that's too much' and offered to look in my purse to find a smaller coin. He must have slid out that 20 euro note at the same time. I did not even notice until an hour later. I felt so stupid.\" According to neuroscientists, the key requirement for a successful pickpocket is not having nifty fingers, it's having a working knowledge of the loopholes in our brain. The most important of these loopholes is the fact that our bra...\n\nQ: What will the author probably talk about next?", "options": ["Mom's another suffering", "Pickpockets concerning new technology", "Pickpockets' tricks", "Apollo Robbins' stage pickpockets"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1421, "question": "The Internet has led to a huge increase in credit-card fraud.Your card information can even be on sale on an illegal website.Websites offering cheap goods and services should be regarded with care.Online shoppers who enter their credit-card information may never receive the goods they thought they had bought. The thieves then go shopping with your card number--or sell the information over the Internet.Computer hackers have broken down security system, raising questions about the safety of card holder information. Several months ago, 25,000 customers of a CD universe, an online music retailer , were not lucky.Their names, addresses and credit-card numbers were posted on a Website after the retailer refused to pay $ 157,828 to get back the information.Credit-card firms are now fighting again...\n\nQ: According to this passage most people worry about shopping on the Internet because   _  .", "options": ["a great number of stolen credit-cards are sold on the Internet every day", "fraud on the Internet happens very often", "many Websites break down every day", "there are too many illegal Websites on the Internet"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 722, "question": "Mattel Inc. is _ 4.4 million Polly Pocket toys with magnets after some of them caused serious injuries to children who swallowed magnets that fell off. Tiny magnets inside the toys may fall off without being noticed by parents and babysitters. The magnets can be swallowed or placed in children's noses or ears. When more than one magnet is swallowed, the magnets can attract each other and cause intestine perforation which can be deadly. The Consumer Product Safety Commission(CPSC)received 170 reports of the small magnets coming out of these recalled toys. There were three reports of serious injuries to children who swallowed more than one magnet. All three suffered intestinal perforations that required operation. A 2-year-old child stayed in hospital for seven days and a 7-year-old child wa...\n\nQ: All of the following points are covered in the story EXCEPT  _  .", "options": ["the danger of small magnets", "the ways of returning Polly Pocket toys", "the methods of recognizing a recalled Polly Pocket toys", "the apology made by Mattel Inc."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2479, "question": "We live in a dangerous world. The figures for crime go up year by year. If you were attacked in the street, would you be able to defend yourself? Not very well probably, especially if someone was pointing a gun at you. We all see a lot of violence of films, but recently some programs on television showed how people can defend themselves without guns. For example, in one film a woman was attacked from behind. She threw the man, who was heavier and stronger than she was, over her head. Then she held him tightly on the ground. How? She knew Judo. Jiu-jitsu, as judo is sometimes called, means \"muscle science\" in Japanese. The student of judo needs to learn a lot about the body, its bones and muscles. Judo uses a number of \"falls\", \"holds\" and \"throws\". Someone who does not know judo cannot def...\n\nQ: According to passage, in fact \"judo\" is   _  .", "options": ["the same as \"Jiu-jitsu\"", "a kind of fighting", "a kind of muscle science", "is helpful to a strong man"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 865, "question": "Most people who live in Seattle, Washington, love their city. There is a never-ending flow of fun things to do. But, people who live there do not always enjoy the day-after-day absence of sunshine during the winter months. It is documented fact that sunshine (or lack of it) plays a major role in how each of us meets the day. It also affects how we perform at school or work. When people are derived of sunlight, they can develop seasonal affective disorder, which makes it difficult for them to feel happy or get things accomplished. No major city in the United States is more affected by the \"sunshine factor\" than Seattle. To fight drizzle and fog during the winter months, Steve Murphy created a business that is very popular among the locals. The Indoor Sun Shoppe is more than a little ray of ...\n\nQ: Which of the following best defines the term seasonal affective disorder in Para.2?", "options": ["mild temperature and a general feeling of illness caused by gray winter", "exhaustion, depression and lack of energy caused by a lack of sunlight", "winter-related illness caused by the low temperature and little sunlight", "post-holiday depression that comes when relatives leave after Christmas"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1017, "question": "A group of graduates, well established in their careers, were talking at a reunion and decided to visit their old university professor, now retired. During their visit, the conversation turned to complaints about stress in their work and lives. Offering his guests hot chocolate, the professor went into the kitchen and returned with a large pot of hot chocolate and other things including cups-porcelain , glass, crystal, some plain looking, some expensive, some elegant -- telling them to help themselves to the hot chocolate. When they all had a cup of hot chocolate in hand, the professor said: \"I notice that all the nice looking and expensive cups were taken, leaving behind the plain and cheap ones. While it is normal for you to want only the best for yourselves, that is the source of your p...\n\nQ: When did they decide to go to see their professor?", "options": ["After the reunion.", "During the get-together.", "Before they graduated.", "Just after the professor retired."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2981, "question": "Family Vs Technology Modern technology certainly changes family behavior, but does it really damage family life as many people fear? Not necessarily, says Dr. Silva, a professor in Sociology at the Open University, she also argues it is wrong to assume technology erodes(,) the quality of family life. \"There is the idea that technology has an influence on the family and the family suffers. My take is quite different,\" she explains. \"Technological change happens because people's lives change. And it is people's choices of how to live that creates processes of innovation as well. The family has a role like the economy or like technology itself in changing the world. The imagination is important in driving the things technologists want to find for our daily lives. People desire to see nature a...\n\nQ: What is Dr. Silva's attitude towards the effect that technology has on family life?", "options": ["Worried.", "Optimistic .", "Puzzled.", "Uncertain."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1267, "question": "The International Voluntary Service runs a number of Youth Exchanges throughout the year.Youth Exchanges give small groups of 4-5 young people the opportunity to take part in volunteering trips abroad for an average of two weeks.These young people are joined by 4-5 young people from 3-4 other nationalities and are a wonderful intercultural experience in a safe environment. Example Youth Exchanges: Youth Exchange 1 Location:Ireland Other nationalities:Ireland,Spain,Italy,Hungary Theme:Focuses on the topic of community reconstruction and community activities--exploring how local issues facing our communities are connected to global issues.The group will also learn about the eco-village as an example of a community and take part in team-building activities. Youth Exchange 2 Location:France Ot...\n\nQ: What do you focus on when travelling in France?", "options": ["Gardening work.", "Civil rights", "Developing social inclusion.", "Rebuilding communities"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2953, "question": "The southwest of Australia has been named as one of 25\"hot spots\" for future species extinction because of global warming.A new study says global warming will become a top cause of extinction across the world,with thousands of species of plantsand animals likely to be wiped out in the coming decades. According to the study,global warming ranks among the most serious threats to the planet's biodiversity and,under some conditions,may be more than that due to deforestation.This study provides even stronger scientific evidence that global warming will result in catastrophic species losses across the planet.Last month,a UN study said humans were responsible for the worst extinction and urged extra efforts to reach a UN target of slowing the rate of losses by 2010. Scientists disagree about how ...\n\nQ: According to the passage,which of the following about Australia is TRUE?", "options": ["Australia possesses the richest species in the world.", "Australia is the country with the highest rate of extinction.", "The species in the southwest of Australia will be easily affected by global warming.", "Australia will have the highest temperature in the world."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3233, "question": "This Monday,the nation will start to celebrate Presidents' Day,just seven days before George Washington's birthday.Everyone agrees that day is a holiday,but is it just to celebrate George Washington's Birthday? What about Abraham Lincoln? Some government offices call it Presidents' Day.Others say the holiday is officially Washington's Birthday.Confused yet? George Washington was elected the country's first President on April 30,1789.Soon after,Americans began publicly celebrating his birthday.Presidential historians say the actual date of George Washington's birth is February 11,1732.But a change in the calendar system 20 years later shifted all dates,making Washington's birthday February 22,which is now well accepted.In 1879.Congress made Washington's birthday an official federal holiday....\n\nQ: What can we infer from the passage?", "options": ["Washington's Birthday is the same as Lincoln's.", "The change in the calendar system was not wise.", "The new act changed the holiday's name.", "This Monday is the third one of this February."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2564, "question": "Ten years ago,Morgan Zuch,a two--year--old girl from Long Island,New York,was diagnosed with leukemia .The day that Morgan's father Rod knew it,he made a promise,\"If my daughter gets better,I will devote the rest of my life to helping others who are in the Same condition.\" Fortunately.Morgan recovered gradually,and since then,Rod and his wife Nancy,have been helping other families with cancer.stricken children through the Morgan Center.It is the country's first preschool for children with cancer. Because of the risk of germs, children with cancer are usually forbidden from playing with other kids.They must spend their days in hospital rooms or lying in bed at home.The Zuchs believed that children with cancer should have the opportunity to play,too. The center offers the kids and their fami...\n\nQ: The Zuchs created the Morgan Center  _  .", "options": ["to help their daughter to realize her dream", "to invite other children to play with their daughter", "to build a school for their daughter and her friends", "to provide a healthy place for children with cancer"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1623, "question": "On October 12, 1989, some Chinese scientists were working at the computers to look for information they needed. Suddenly they saw a lot of very bright spots crossing the computers's screens. At the same time the computers were working much slower. To find out what was happening they stopped their work to check some parts of the computers. To their horror, they found out that most of their stored information was got rid of by computer viruses ! Obviously all these computers had been infected by computer viruses. It is said that the computer viruses were made by a group of young men fond of playing tricks. They all had excellent education. They created the viruses just to show their intelligence . These kinds of computer viruses are named Jerusalem Viruses. These viruses can stay in computer...\n\nQ: The group of young men created the virus to  _  .", "options": ["damage the computers", "test their ability", "tell the world that they were intelligent", "play a trick on operators of the computers"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2136, "question": "When my son was just learning to talk, I carried him around the house in my arms and pointed out things to him. \"Look, David, a clock. \"He'd smile and point as I did and say \"clock\". David was quick at connecting the shape of things to their words. When my son was about four years old, I walked with him to the backyard. I knew that there was an ant colony under one of the slate stones in the walkway near the shed, so I said to David, \"Come on. I want to show you something. \" As I showed David the ants that were crawling around the slate stone, he crouched down on his legs and looked with great intensity at the ants. For days after that, David wanted to look under every rock in the garden, and we often found worms, ants and so on. I recognized that David loved to look at things closely and ...\n\nQ: The author showed David the ants to   .", "options": ["prevent him from becoming bored", "develop his enthusiasm for observation", "teach him some new words", "arouse his interest in creatures"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3326, "question": "It seems that men are under more stress when stuck in a traffic jam than women. British researchers for the GPS company TomTom used saliva to decide the stress levels. Levels for women were far lower than levels for men. Most of the people taking part in the research, men and women, reported that they didn't feel any stress at all. Even with that report, their saliva told a different story. In fact, people are under stress while in traffic and not even realizing it. That does not mean good things for health. People can only do something about their health if they know something is wrong. Men are more likely to have much less patience than women. That is why their stress levels are much higher than women when they are sitting still in traffic. Men want to get where they are going now. 72% o...\n\nQ: What people reported were different from the research findings because  _  .", "options": ["they didn't know they were stressed", "they didn't know how to describe their feelings", "they didn't want to share their true feelings with others", "they didn't want to admit something was wrong with themselves"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 769, "question": "As shocking as the idea of baby birds growing up in a cigarette-filled home sounds, a new study suggests that some birds may benefit from putting the stuff from cigarette butts into their nests. The nicotine remaining in smoked filters may serve as a natural insecticide , driving harmful insects away from the nests and the baby birds living within. Tobacco plants produce nicotine because it defends against insects that would otherwise eat the plants. The butts are undoubtedly smelly. But birds are actually quite fond of smelly chemicals, such as those found in aromatic plants. Some nest-building species regularly fill their nests with fresh aromatics, possibly because the chemicals are good for the immune system or the development of the chicks. Alternatively, the plant chemicals might act...\n\nQ: What can you infer from the passage?", "options": ["Birds tend to use insecticide to protect the baby birds.", "Nicotine is the only chemical that drives harmful insects away.", "Some insects are afraid of smelly chemicals in aromatic plants.", "Unsmoked cigarette traps attract more harmful insects."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2578, "question": "Just five one-hundredths of an inch thick, light golden in color1 and with a perfect \"saddle curl,\" the Lay's potato chip seems an unlikely weapon for global domination. But its maker, Frito-Lay, thinks otherwise. \"Potato chips are a snack food for the world,\" said Salman Amin, the company's head of global marketing. Amin believes there is no corner of the world that can resist the charms of a Frito-Lay potato chip. Frito-Lay is the biggest snack maker in prefix = st1 /Americaowned by PepsiCo and accounts for over half of the parent company's $3 billion annual profits. But theU.S.snack food market is largely saturated, and to grow the company has to look overseas. Its strategy rests on two beliefs: first a global product offers economies of scale with which local brands cannot compete. And...\n\nQ: It is the belief of Foito-Lay's head of global marking that  _  .", "options": ["Potato chips can hardly be used as a weapon to dominate the world market", "People all over the world enjoy eating their company's potato chips", "The light golden color1 enhances the charm of their company's potato chips", "Their company must find new ways to promote domestic sales"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2881, "question": "On the way home from school, Jack always passes a park. His mother said it was dangerous to pass by the park at night, but it is the fastest way home. Today, after finishing soccer practice, Jack was walking toward the park as usual. Suddenly, Jack heard someone calling him, \"Excuse me!\" Jack turned around, and there was an old woman. \"Yes, ma'am.\" Jack answered politely. \"Don't pass by the park tonight.\" Her voice was weak and dry. \"Okay, ma'am,\" said Jack carelessly. The old woman held Jack's hand strongly, and said, \"I mean it!\" Jack felt the hairs on his neck stand up. As soon as the lady let go of his hand, he started to run. This time, he ran so fast that he didn't have time to think where he was going. When he stopped, he realized he was in the middle of the park. He remembered what...\n\nQ: Why did the old lady prevent Jack from passing by the park?", "options": ["Jack's mother asked her to do so.", "In case he might disturb their work.", "In case he might be frightened.", "She was doing a secret job there."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 794, "question": "When I opened my e-mail the other day, a pretty woman named Rachel appeared on my computer screen. She greeted me by name and started talking with great enthusiasm . Every now and then she stopped to smile at me or blow a kiss. She was reading to me an e-mail from my brother, and a lot of it was about the trouble he had getting the phone company to give him a high-speed Internet connection. It was pretty cool. Rachel was there thanks to a new technology called Facemail. An ace man lets you send an e-mail that gets ready to the recipient by an attractive male or female from or by a clown . The software, which is free, can be downloaded at www.facemail.com. Facemail faces are lifelike, and they simulate emotions based on emotions-for example, that you put in your text. Type in; -x, and Rache...\n\nQ: The pretty woman that appears on the writer's computer screen was_.", "options": ["his brother's girl friend", "not a real person", "the picture of his pen friend", "a woman working on the Internet"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2053, "question": "From the same place that brought you the Robot Suit HAL comes the \"motorized knee\".Designed by researchers at Japan's Tsukuba University, the device supports the flex( ) of the knee, which enables a runner to use 30% less muscle power compared to running unassisted. Coming in a kit , the device consists of a small motor that helps flex the knee, a sensor that detects the knees' degree of flex, and a safety lever --all of which attach to the user's leg.The user is also forced to carry a backpack that holds a control unit and battery to power the motor.All up the device weighs around 5kg,which will probably lessen the performance benefits of wearing the device somewhat.In experiments runners wearing the device could jog at 7.5kmh, which is hardly anything special--but predictably they could ...\n\nQ: To make sure that the device runs smoothly,  _  .", "options": ["the user should be equipped with other related units", "the device should be improved through experiments", "the user shouldn't be physically handicapped", "the device should be smaller and lighter"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1824, "question": "Thank-you cards -- heartfelt expressions of gratitude for gifts, services and general kindness -- seem to be rare in an age when the Internet continues to reduce human touch. Although our society has changed greatly over the past century, the _ of thank-you notes has not. While most people would agree that thank-you notes under these conditions are a necessity, there are still those who forever delay or are forgetful for unknown reasons. And at no time of the year are thank-you notes more visible (or lacking) than June, the month of graduations, and the beginning of summer parties. \" It' s a must-do thing. A real ' thank you' does not come by e-mail. It comes in the mail in an envelope. And what comes out of an envelope is a beautiful thing to touch and to handle and to pass around for eve...\n\nQ: Nowadays thank-you cards seem to be rare mainly because   _  .", "options": ["People think that they are out of fashion", "It is cheaper to say thanks by e-mail", "The Internet has reduced our chances of getting together", "People are too busy to remember these things"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2321, "question": "One of the most famous basketball-players in the New Castle's history was paralyzed in a wheelchair one day...and was walking the next. Citizens of New Castle simply refer to it as \"The Miracle\". Joel Haler woke up in his dorm room at Hope College last October totally paralyzed from the waist down. Four hospitals later, the only way he could walk was through Robotic Walking Treatment. \"This past Tuesday, I was doing the Robotic walk and lasted ten minutes,\" Joel said. After that, he gave up. Joel wanted to accept the inevitable and cancelled his next Robotic Walking Treatment appointment. Then, the night before his cancelled appointment, he woke up to a terrible pain. An hour and a half later, the serious pain left him with an unusual feeling in his legs. \"As it continued to move up my leg...\n\nQ: Which part of Joel Haler's body didn't work?", "options": ["His whole body.", "His legs and feet.", "His arms and hands.", "His arms and legs"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1239, "question": "Generational differences and the economy are shifting more responsibilities for children from their parents to grandparents, according to a new survey. More than one-third of grandparents aged 50 and older contribute financially to their grandchildren's upbringing, and 11 percent have a grandchild living with them, the poll by AARP, the group for 36 million older US citizens, showed. Forty percent of people who responded to the telephone survey, whose average age was 69, reported spending more than $500 on grandchildren over the past year beyond traditional gifts.Education costs accounted for 53 percent, daily expenses for 37 percent and medical costs for 23 percent.Sixteen percent provided daycare for grandchildren. \"They are the safety net for American families, helping to pay for practi...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE about grandparents?", "options": ["Most of them have grandchildren of a different race.", "One third keep in touch with their grandchildren via email.", "Nearly 40 percent discussed dating with more than one grandchild.", "About three fifths communicate with their grandchildren at least once a week."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2260, "question": "From Nigerian science fiction to a time-travelling serial killer, Brittle Paper selects the best works of fiction from the continent to inspire our inner desire to travel. My Life in the Bush of Ghosts - Amos Tutuola Who wouldn't want to get enveloped in a fog of magical delight? The novel describes the adventures of a little boy lost in a forest. His search for the way back home seem to take him deeper and deeper into secret colonies of creatures living in reality. Nigerians in Space - Deji Olukotun Wale is a Nigerian lunar geologist. He is under the spell of a life-long dream to traveling out to the moon when the mysterious Mr Bello offers him the chance to man a Nigerian space-exploration mission. But like most dreams, what starts out as the magical fulfillment of desire quickly slips i...\n\nQ: Which of the following authors writes a story about traveling by sea?", "options": ["Laila Lalami", "Amos Tutuola", "Deji Olukotun", "Ama Ata Aidoo"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 93, "question": "According to Andrew, it never would have happened if he had not had a flat tire on Highway 10 last night at about 7:30. He was on his way to attend a three-day sales meeting when he had the flat. tyre. Unfortunately, he did not have a spare, so he pushed the car off the road, locked it up, and managed to thumb a ride back to Pine Grove. It was after eleven o'clock when he finally got home, and it was then that his real problems started. When Andrew left home at about 5:30, he had told his wife not to expect him back until Thursday or Friday. Knowing that his wife was nervous about staying in the house alone at night, Andrew took the precaution of checking all the windows in the house to be sure they were locked, so that he could report to his wife that the house was secure. He convinced hi...\n\nQ: When Andrew was approaching the house  _  .", "options": ["he was sure he would pleasently surprise his wife", "he was deep in thought", "he was sure that his neighbor would help him", "he was worried about how to wake his wife up"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 437, "question": "Teenage life is quite dramatic but that doesn't mean you cannot enjoy your life in these years. Even with your daily troubles, your life is not very hard if you know how to deal with them. I know exactly how you feel. Life as a teenager can be hard. You are not a kid anymore, because you are smart enough to observe and analyze your surroundings. However, you are still not an adult because there are still lots of experiences that you need to have and lessons that you need to learn from these experiences. To top it all, the hormonal imbalance in your body can really mess you up emotionally. I have been there. I was in it for 6 years exploring what life is about. As a teenager, I had a major problem with completing my chores on time. And at that time, all that I need to do was finish my assig...\n\nQ: The author tries to persuade readers mainly by means of   _  .", "options": ["quoting famous sayings by famous people", "setting his own experiences as example", "listing all of his troubles in his childhood", "showing the numerous assignments for children"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1737, "question": "Names have gained increasing importance in the competitive world of higher education. As colleges struggle for market share, they are looking for names that project the image they want or reflect the changes they hope to make. Trenton State College, for example, became the College of New Jersey nine years ago when it began raising admission standards and appealing to students from throughout the state. \"All I hear in higher education is, 'Brand, brand, brand,'\" said Tim Westerbeck, who specializes in branding and is managing director of Lippmann Hearne, a marketing firm based in Chicago that works with universities and other nonprofit organizations. \"There has been a sea change over the last 10 years. Marketing used to be almost a dirty word in higher education.\" Not all efforts at name ch...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT the reason for colleges to change their names?", "options": ["They prefer higher education competition.", "They try to gain advantage in market share.", "They want to project their image.", "They hope to make some changes."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 735, "question": "When we donate blood, a small amount is usually taken in advance for at least ABO and Rh systems typing. If you are O+, the O is your ABO type and the + is your Rh type. It is possible to be A, B, AB, or O as well as Rh + or Rh-. The ABO system was discovered by Karl Landsteiner in the early 1900s. He was awarded the Nobel Prize for his achievements. There are four basic types of blood in the ABO system: A, B, AB and O. Everybody is born with one of these four types of blood. We get blood type, just like hair color and height from parents. Because of the substances contained in each type, the four groups must be _ carefully, If two different blood types are mixed together, it may put a person into an extremely dangerous situation. Basically, A and B cannot be mixed. A and B cannot receive ...\n\nQ: The writer suggests that the third most common blood type among the Europeans is   _  .", "options": ["B", "A", "AB", "O"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 683, "question": "For the first time in Hong Kong's history, an entertainer has been written into middle school textbooks. He is considered one of the best actors in Hong Kong. Yes, he is Chow Yun-fat. The example of his long hard struggle for success has been used in a chapter in a Hong Kong middle school textbook. Using his experience, students can learn to make the most of their time and to grab every opportunity to succeed. On hearing about this, Chow said happily, \"I really hope that my experiences can make young people understand that one should not be afraid of difficulties and setbacks , for they are the only way to success.\" Indeed, Chow has travelled a long and difficult path to reach his success. In 1955, he was born into a poor family in Hong Kong. When he was 17, he had to leave school. He work...\n\nQ: What can we infer from the passage?", "options": ["Chow Yun-fat is proud of his success.", "Chow Yun-fat prefers to make a living by selling cameras rather than by performing.", "Chow Yun-fat has won more awards than other actors.", "Chow Yun-fat is popular both at home and abroad."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 992, "question": "In the United States, the legal age to drink alcohol is twenty-one --- one of the highest in the world. Americans debate whether _ should be lowered, or whether young drinkers would only drink more. In parts of Europe, the legal drinking age for beer, and sometimes hard liquor, is sixteen. Yet France may raise the age limit for beer and wine sales to eighteen, the same as for hard liquor there. Rules on alcohol differ from college to college in the United States. Many schools require all first-year students to take an alcohol prevention and education program, often given online. Some have a \"zero tolerance\" policy where alcohol is banned from all buildings. Parents are informed of violations and students may be suspended . At the University of Virginia in Charlottesville, permission is nee...\n\nQ: If a student under 21 drinks alcohol for the first time in Virginia,he might   _  .", "options": ["drop out of school.", "require an alcohol education program.", "be tried and sentenced to a year or so in prison.", "be fined five hundred dollars as well as fifty hours of community service."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2636, "question": "I took the bus to work for many years. No one knew each other; the passengers all sat there sleepily in the morning. The bus was cheerless and silent. One of the passengers was a small gray-haired man who took the bus to the center for senior citizens every morning. No one ever paid very much attention to him. One July morning he said good morning to the driver and smiled. The driver nodded guardedly . The rest of us were silent. The next day, the old man boarded with a big smile and said in a loud voice: \"A very good morning to you all!\" Some of us looked up, amazed, and murmured \"Good Morning\" in reply. The following weeks, our friend was dressed in a nice old suit and tie. His thin hair had been carefully combed. He said good morning to us every day and we gradually began to nod and tal...\n\nQ: Which of the following is not true?", "options": ["The atmosphere on the bus was cheerful and lively at first.", "People were surprised at the old man's first greeting.", "People were worried about the old man's absence.", "People on the bus at last shared happiness and sorrow together."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 580, "question": "Read the following reviews for movies that are showing at the moment. And then answer questions. Happiness(Romance) Happinesstells the story of two people (Lisa Turbot and Danny Roy) who work for different advertising companies. They talk on the phone all the time and don't like each other. But then they _ by e-mail and fall in love. This movie will be very popular with teenagers and people who like romances. It also has beautiful music. I Scream(Thriller) InI Scream, Paul (Colin Jacks) is a young man who joins a thriller club. Each of the members tries to frighten the others. Paul is told to stay in an old house for the night. Everyone who has tried to stay in the house before has died. This movie is very frightening but also quite silly. It doesn't make sense for Paul to stay in the hous...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the best title for the fourth film?", "options": ["A Hard-working Trick Driver", "Medicine", "A Strange Illness", "Twelve Hours"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 199, "question": "We produce 500 billion of plastic bags in a year worldwide and they are thrown away polluting oceans, killing wildlife and getting dumped in landfills where they take up to 1000 years to decompose. Researchers have been unsuccessfully looking for a solution. The 16-year old Canadian high school student, Daniel Burd, from Waterloo Collegiate Institute, has discovered a way to make plastic bags degrade in as few as 3 months, a finding that won him first prize at the Canada-Wide Science Fair, a $10 000 prize, a $20 000 scholarship, and a chance to revolutionize a major environmental issue. Burd's strategy was simple: Since plastic does eventually degrade, it must be eaten by microorganisms . If those microorganisms could be identified, we could put them to work eating the plastic much faster ...\n\nQ: Daniel Burd exposed one plastic sample to dead bacteria to   _  .", "options": ["make the live bacteria work better", "test how effective his method was", "know which bacteria worked faster", "control the temperature in the process"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3408, "question": "Friendly doctors are\"bad for their patients'health\",researchers have warned as a new study revealed two thirds of young doctors struggle to be truthful with patients they like. Blurring(...)the lines between social and professional relationships can affect the level of care offered and prevent patients from being honest about important side effects. \"Doctors should avoid adding patients as friends on Facebook,they should not hug or allow patients to call them by their first names\".regulators have warned.\"Those who break the boundaries will face some punishment.\" It comes as a survey of 338 oncologists under the age of 40,found 59 per cent said they found it difficult to tell the truth to those patients they liked.Sixty per cent of respondents said if doctors felt too close to their patient...\n\nQ: Why are ffiendl3,doctors bad for their patients'health?", "options": ["They don't like to cheat patients.", "They are not good at treating patients.", "They find it not easier to be objective to the patients.", "They seldom blur the relationship with patients."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1103, "question": "\"Family\" is of course an _ word. But when British people say that their society is based on family life, they are thinking of \"family\" in its narrow, peculiarly European sense of mother ,father and children living together alone in their own house as an economic and social unit. Thus, every British marriage indicates the beginning of a new and independent family--hence the tremendous importance of marriage in British life. For both the man and the woman, marriage means leaving one's parents and starting one's own life. The man's first duty will then be to his wife, and the wife's to her husband. He will be entirely responsible for her financial support, and she for the running of the new home. Their children will be their common responsibility and theirs alone. Neither the wife's parents n...\n\nQ: What does the author mean by \"Family is of course an elastic word\"?", "options": ["Different families have different ways of life.", "Different definitions could be given to the word.", "Different nations have different families.", "Different times produce different families."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3145, "question": "My heroes are the Singapore Women's Everest Team.In 2009,they became the first all-women team to climb Mount Everest.The team of six young women trained for seven years before they climbed the mountain.It was difficult for them to train because Singapore doesn't have any snow or any mountains.But they didn't stop,and in the end they made it.They Worked hard every day for their dream so I really admire them. ----Lance Reed, 16, from Britain My mum,Mary Evans,is a real hero.I have a very big family, with two brothers and three sisters.My mum works very hard every day to look after us, and she is very busy.She always makes time for everyone and she always listens to me if I have a problem.I really respect my mum because she always looks after my family and makes sure we have everything we nee...\n\nQ: Who is closest to his hero?", "options": ["Mark.", "William.", "Richard.", "Lance."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 202, "question": "Reading can be a social activity. Think of the people who belong to book groups. They choose books to read and then meet m discuss them. Now, the website BookCrossing.com rums the page on the traditional idea of a book group. Members go on the site and register books they own that they would like.sham. BookCrossing provides an identifying numb\" .stick inside the book. Then the person 'releases' the book by leaving it in a public place. The hope is that the book will have an adventure, traveling far and wide with each new reader who finds it. Bruce Pederson is the chief executive of BookCrossing. He and his wife Hearer started the site with Ron Hombaker in 2001. Mr. Pederson says, \"One of the founding principles was the two things that change your life: tha people you meet and the books you...\n\nQ: What should a member do first before releasing a book?", "options": ["Register the back online.", "Leave the book in a coffee shop.", "Stick an identifying number on it.", "Remind~m read it."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2771, "question": "Have you got any wonderful plans for your coming winter vacation? Here are some wonderful films for you to kill time....\n\nQ: If you bring your seven-year-old sister to the cinema, which of the following film should you avoid?", "options": ["Away We Go.", "Orphan.", "2012.", "500 Days of Summer."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1819, "question": "I want to tell you a story that changed my life many years ago. We were living in College Station, Texas and my wife and I were on our way home from Houston, Texas one Saturday morning. We decided to stop at a local restaurant to get something to eat since we had enough time. When we finished, we got back into our car and before I started it, we noticed a homeless man standing in front of the building. His clothes were worn and it looked as though he didn't have any money. It was cold and I was sure he wanted something warm to drink; however, it was not this that I remember, because that is not what \"moved\" me. A dog was also walking up to the front of the building. Being a dog owner, I knew that the dog was a mother, and that she had just had some pups . She was hungry and weak and I felt...\n\nQ: Which of the following would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["My Memory", "A Poor Dog", "The Homeless Person", "A Mother Dog"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2382, "question": "I was in my third year of teaching writing at Ralph High School in New York, when one of my students,15-year-old Mikey,gave me a note from his mother.It explained his absence from class the day before: \"Dear Mr. McCort,Mikey's grandmother,who is eighty years of age,fell down the stairs from too much coffee and I kept Mikey at home to take care of her and his baby sister so I couldn't go to my job. Please excuse Mikey and he'll do his best in the future.P.S.His grandmother is OK.\" I had seen Mikey writing the note at his desk.I said nothing.Most parental-excuse note, I received were penned by my students.The writers of those notes didn't realize that honest excuse notes were usually dull: \"Peter was late because the alarm clock didn't go off.\" The students always said it was hard putting 20...\n\nQ: Why did the author's heart sink?", "options": ["He thought the headmaster would scold him.", "The heated discussions angered the headmaster.", "The students were not behaving themselves.", "The headmaster was looking at his students' papers."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1429, "question": "Money spent on advertising is money spent as well as any I know of.It serves directly to assist a rapid distribution of goods at reasonable prices, thereby establishing a firm home market and so making it possible to provide for export at competitive prices.By drawing attention to new ideas it helps enormously to raise standards of living.By helping to increase demand it ensures an increased need for labour, and is therefore an effective way to fight unemployment.It lowers the costs of many services: without advertisements your daily newspaper would cost four times as much, the price of your television license would need to be doubled, and travel by bus or tube would cost 20 per cent more. And perhaps most important of all, advertising provides a guarantee of reasonable value in the produc...\n\nQ: Which of the following opinions does the author probably accept?", "options": ["There is nothing wrong with advertising in persuading buyers.", "Advertising can prevent low-quality articles from entering markets.", "Advertising informs people of new ideas rather than wins them over.", "Buyers are not interested in getting information from advertisements."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3048, "question": "Schoolgirls have been wearing such short skirts at Paget High School in Branston that they've been ordered to wear trousers instead. All skirts will be banned from September. Tight-fitting trousers will also be forbidden and Muslim head-dresses will have to be \"school blue'' color. Head teacher Don Smith said, \"One of the big problems for us at the school has been the number of girls who have been wearing inappropriately short skirts. This has been an area of particular concern at a time when there has been a lot of material nationally about the sexualisation of young people.\" He also said, \" It will be impractical to police the length of girls' skirts. A blanket ban will be easier for staff to put into practice. We did not want to arrive at a situation where we were telling girls their sk...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that   _", "options": ["the new uniform rules are well received by everyone", "no schools in Branston allow girls to wear short skirts", "parents unable to afford the new uniform will gain support", "the pupils' parents were informed of the new clothing policy"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 859, "question": "In the decade of the 1970s, the United Nations organized several important meetings on the human environment to study a very serious problem.We humans are destroying the world around us.We must learn to protect them, or life will be very bad for our children and grandchildren. There are several major aspects to this problem. Population Most problems of the environment come from population growth.In 1700 there were 635 million people in the world; in 1900 there were 1.6 billion; in 1950, 2.5 billion; and in 1980, 4.4 billion.In the year 2010 there will be 7.3 billion.More people need more water, more food, more wood, and more petroleum. Distribution Scientists say there is enough water in the world for everyone, but some countries have a lot of water and some have only a little.Some areas g...\n\nQ: The best title of the passage should be   _", "options": ["The World Being Destroyed", "A Serious Problem We Should Pay Attention to", "Aspects That Destroyed Our World", "Conserving the World's Natural Resources"], "answer": 3}]